Zhuhe Cui

Full Stack Web Developer

25 Tai Ching Fe Wai Seung Ko Hong Kong HongKong, New York, 854934 janisflores360@gmail.com 65748647

Dedicated and efficient full stack developer with 6+ years experience in application layers, presentation layers, and databases. Certified in both F/E and B/E technologies. Spearheaded successful transition from LAMP stack to MEAN which cut latency by 40% and increased effectiveness of database administrators by 20%. Seeking to further improve HTML5 and CSS3 skills as the future full stack developer at Atmospheric Solutions.

Key Skills

- HTML, CSS, JavaScript, PHP
- React JS & Angular JS
- jQuery
- SQL Databases & MongoDB
- Android App Development
- Flux/Redux
- CI/CD & DevOps

Professional Experience

New York, NY BravDev | April 2018 - Present

- Used understanding of React fundamentals to promote better component lifecycle practices, increasing turnaround speed by 23% with 100% deadline adherence.
- Communicated with other teams and senior management to adapt 50+ clients' websites to adapt to changing industry standards.
- Introduced wider use of isomorphic React and Node.js for web applications, decreasing load times by roughly 35%.
- Followed documentation to always remain up-to-speed on what needs to be updated in response to new release versions.

New York, NY

Murray Hill Media Group | December 2016 - February 2018

Key Qualifications & Responsibilities

- Implemented websites, mobile applications, and landing pages from concept through deployment.
- Standardized all output with a new, responsive, mobile-first approach and strategy.
- Assessed UX and UI designs for technical feasibility.
- Developed standard and ad hoc reports in graph format as required.
- Collaborated with product team members to implement new feature developments.

Key Achievements

 Implemented new responsive, mobile-first approach which increased mobile traffic by 20%

Seattle, WA

Amazon | January 2013 - June 2016

- Design and develop web applications using various programming languages and frameworks
- Collaborate with team members to identify and solve technical issues
- Conduct code reviews and provide feedback to team members
- Implement security measures to protect web applications from cyber attacks
- Maintain and update existing web applications

Education

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science

Hong Kong University of Science and Technology at Clear Water Bay | September 2014 - 2016

Relevant Coursework: Computer Fundamentals, Web Development, Typography, Web Design, eColor Theory, Database Management Systems, Object-Oriented Programming, Web Architecture, Mobile Application Developmen